Finding Aid Title T003
Rockefeller Archive Center
John Smith papers
Bulk, 2000-2001
date expression
T003
Rockefeller Archive Center
12.0 cubic ft. Container Summary
Abstract note content
Dimensions note content
General Physical Description note content
Material Specific Details note content
Physical Facet note content
A Book Apart.
Aiken, Susan Hardy, 1943-
Winona Test
Benedict, Karen M.
Winona test2.
Winona Test3
Accruals note
Accruals note content
Appraisal note
Appraisal note content
Arrangement note
Arrangement note content
Biographical/Historical note
Chronology Title
Chronology Event Date 2 Chronology Event Description 3 Chronology Event Description 4
Chronology Event Date 1 Chronology Event Description 1 Chronology Event Description 2
List Title
List Label
List Item Value 1
List Label
List Item Value 2
List Ordered Title
List Item Value 1
List Item Value 2
Text note content
Conditions Governing Access note
Conditions Governing Access note content
Custodial History note
Custodial History note content
Existence and Location of Copies note
Existence and Location of Copies note content
Existence and Location of Originals note
Existence and Location of Originals note content
File Plan note
File Plan note content
General note
General note content
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Immediate Source of Acquisition note content
Note content
Item Value Reference Text
Item Value Reference Text
Legal Status note
Legal Status note content
Other Finding Aids note
Other Finding Aids note content
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note content
Publication Note
For a current list of known publications related to the archival collections of the Rockefeller Archive Center, see the Bibliography of Scholarship at the Rockefeller Archive Center http://www.rockarch.org/publications/biblio/scholarship.pdf
Item Value 1
Item Value 2
Related Archival Materials note
Related Archival Materials note content
Separated Materials note
Separated Materials note content
Scope and Contents note
Scope and Contents note content
A. Niggli.; Riland, W. Kenneth; New Zealand
- Manuscripts, Bulk, 2000-2001; Date Expression; Component Unique ID 1; 12.0 cubic ft. Container Summary; Abstract note content; Dimensions note content; General Physical Description note content; Material Specific Details note content; Physical Facet note content; Abrash, Barbara; Turner, Thomas Bourne, 1902-
  Accruals note
  Accruals note content
  Appraisal note
  Appraisal note content
  Arrangement note
  Arrangement note content
  Biographical/Historical note
  Biographical/Historical note content
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Conditions Governing Access note content
  Custodial History note
  Custodial History note content
  Existence and Location of Copies note
  Existence and Location of Copies note content
  File Plan note
  File Plan note content
  General note
  General note content
  Immediate Source of Acquisition note
  Immediate Source of Acquisition note content
  Index note content
  Item Value 1 Reference Text
  Item Value 2 Reference Text
  Legal Status note
  Legal Status note content
  Other Finding Aids note
  Other Finding Aids note content
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note content
  Publication Note
  For a current list of known publications related to the archival collections of the Rockefeller Archive Center, see the Bibliography of Scholarship at the Rockefeller Archive Center http://www.rockarch.org/publications/biblio/scholarship.pdf
  Item Value 1
  Item Value 2
  Related Archival Materials note
  Related Archival Materials note content
  Scope and Contents note
  Scope and Contents note content
  Separated Materials note
  Separated Materials note content
  Existence and Location of Originals note
  Existence... note text
  Acheson, Dean, 1893-1971; Social justice
  - Title of Manuscript, Component Unique ID a (Carton 1, Box 1)
  - Interesting Title of Other Manuscript, Bulk, 1950-1955; 1900-2000; Component Unique ID b; 3.0 cubic ft. Container Summary; Africa Publications Trust.; Perez, Luis, 1904-1962 (Box 1)
    Wall, Joseph Frazier; Strawberries
- Yearbooks, Date Expression; Component Unique ID 2
  - Mary Smith, Date Expression; Component Unique ID a; 1.0 cubic ft. Container Summary; Africa Publications Trust.; American Council for the Arts in Education
    Aldrich, Nelson W. (Nelson Wilmarth), 1841-1915; Africa
    - 1954, Component Unique ID a.1; 1.0 cubic ft. Container Summary
    - 1955, Component Unique ID a.2; 1.0 cubic ft. Container Summary
  - John Smith, Date Expression; Component Unique ID b; 1.0 cubic ft. Container Summary
    - 1955, Component Unique ID b.1; 1.0 cubic ft. Container Summary
    - 1956, Component Unique ID b.2; 1.0 cubic ft. Container Summary
- Correspondence, Date Expression; Component Unique ID 3; 1.0 cubic ft. Container Summary
  Scope and Contents note content (at RG level)
  - Incoming, Date Expression; Component Unique ID a; 1.0 cubic ft. Container Summary
    Scope and Contents note content (at Sub-RG level)
    - Letter from Mary Smith, Date Expression; Component Unique ID a.1; 1.0 cubic ft. Container Summary
  - Outgoing, Date Expression; Component Unique ID b; 1.0 cubic ft. Container Summary
    Scope and Contents note content (Subseries level)
    - Photograph, Date Expression; Component Unique ID b.1; 1.0 cubic ft. Container Summary; Dimensions note text; Gen Phys Desc note text; Material Specific Details note; Phys Facet note; A Book Apart.; A. Niggli. (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Accruals note text
      Appraisal note text
      Arrangement note text
      Bio/Hist note text
      Conditions Governing Access note text
      Custodial History note text
      File Plan note text
      General note text
      Imm Source note text
      Legal Status note text
      Phys Char and Tech Req note content
      Scope note content
      Abrash, Barbara; Africa